[ woman ]
Will .
Hey . I asked
if you were okay .
Sorry .
You know , we don 't
have to do this .
We can just go home .
I 'll be fine .
God , this thing is so ...
thick ...
official .
Maybe they 're
overcompensating .
It 's kind of hard
to call everybody up
out of the blue
after two years .
Nobody 's seen her ?
I ran into her and David
at a supermarket ,
and a little bit
after that , I heard
they disappeared .
And they met
in the grief group ?
Mm-hmm , while we
were still married .
Yeah , I guess you
could have put odds
on our divorce .
No , people
don 't think like that .
Yes , they do .
No , they don 't .
Yes , they -
[ thump ]
- [ gasps ]
Oh , my God .
[ turns off engine ]
Jesus .
What was that ?
A coyote , I think .
[ hazard lights clicking ]
Just stay here .
[ whimpering ]
Oh , man .
[ whines ]
[ raspy breathing ]
[ weak whimpering continues ]
You should go
back in the car .
[ coyote yelps ]
[ whimpering continues ]
[ Will ]
Okay , okay .
[ coyote yelps ]
Oh , my God .
[ blow lands ]
[ tire iron clangs ]
[ door opens ]
[ sighs ]
Jesus .
[ starts engine ]
[ music playing ]
This was your house ?
A lot of money
in Eden 's family .
Wasn 't ever mine .
[ Will , echoing ]
Come on , Ty .
Dinner 's ready .
[ overlapping chatter ]
[ door closes ]
Hey ,
you 're here .
Fucking A.
I win , see ? Hi !
Was there
a betting pool ?
Uh , for entertainment
purposes only .
- Hey .
- Hey , buddy .
I am Gina .
We met at their - -
- Yes .
- Nice to see you .
- Good to see you .
- God , Kira ,
you look
so fucking hot
right now .
Will you bear
a child for us ,
like , right now ?
We 're not kidding .
And , you , I see
you 've almost shed
that dirty dishrag look
that 's so concerning .
What ? I have
a dirty dishrag look ?
Mm , less so now .
- It 's just - -
- What ? Come on .
He did look
like a dishrag .
How are you ?
Eh ...
Is this Kira ?
- That 's me .
- Hi . I 'm Claire .
Hi . Nice to meet you .
Nice to meet you , too .
Hey , Will , I 'm Ben .
Remember me ?
We drove a thriving
business into
the ground together .
Never thrived .
It was thriving
like a motherfucker
for three months ,
and you know it .
Hey , wait .
Where 's Choi ?
Late as usual ,
and I can 't get
any reception
up here either .
Is Eden and , uh - -
I 'm here .
[ chuckles ]
Oh .
Let me look at you , Will .
[ laughs ]
Mm , I missed you .
You , too .
House doesn 't look
very different , does it ?
No , not - - not really .
Well , we 're glad
you 're here .
Oh .
You 're a mess .
[ laughs ]
And you must be Kira .
Hi .
Thank you
for having me .
Will , you remember David .
Of course . Sure .
Will , come here .
Hey .
[ groans ]
I 'm so glad you 're here .
I 'm really glad , man .
Hey , how - - how are you ?
Oh , I 'm brilliant .
I mean , we 've got
a lot to talk about ,
so much
to celebrate tonight .
Kira .
Yes .
Ah .
Oh . Okay .
Beautiful .
What can
I get you to drink ?
No , I-I 'm good .
Uh , I 'd go
with the wine .
It 's an ' 85 Rothschild .
Are you
shitting me ?
Uh , okay ,
what does that mean ?
Oh , Will ,
you 're adorable .
It 's , like , $ 8 million
a bottle , Cro-Mag .
[ David ] Well ,
this night is special .
We shouldn 't save
these things .
We shouldn 't
put off enjoying ...
what we have .
You sure ?
I 'm good .
Yes . Thank you .
Well , since
everybody 's here - -
Except Choi .
Oh , fucking Choi ,
man .
- Fucking Choi .
- All right .
Except Choi , but , you know ,
I guess we 'll just have
to start without him .
Um , first of all ,
welcome to our
little reunion of sorts .
You guys are all
very special to Eden ,
which - - which means
you 're very special to me ,
and we really missed you ,
and we love you .
You know , each and every one
of us is on a journey ,
and we feel
that it 's important
to be on that journey
with the people you love ,
and it 's something
we really , really
have good here .
We want to open up
the house again ,
give it and us
a new start , so ...
let 's raise this
ridiculously expensive
glass of wine
to new beginnings .
Yeah .
- To new beginnings .
- Cheers .
- Salud .
Hey ! Save a glass for me .
[ chuckles ]
This is Sadie .
Sadie ,
meet my friends .
Hey .
- Hey .
- Hi .
So , um ...
how do you guys
know each other ?
Um ...
just friends
in common , I guess .
We met
in Mexico .
Sadie 's
staying here with us
and helping us out .
Yeah .
It 's fun . We have fun .
[ laughter ]
Hope you don 't mind me
crashing the party .
It 's awesome .
Huh .
They 've told me
so much about you .
[ guitar music
playing on stereo ]
[ Kira ] We hit a coyote
on the way up here .
- What ?
It just came
out of nowhere .
I mean , there was
nothing we could do .
It was
in horrible shape .
He had to kill it .
What ? How did you
not tell us this ,
like , immediately ?
You killed it
with , like , what ?
Tire iron .
Oh , God . What ?
I don 't know
how you did it , man .
That 's pretty butch .
No , it was
a good thing .
That was mercy .
Mm-hmm .
Would you mind
if I looked around
for a little bit ?
Of course not .
Thank you .
See you in a bit .
[ Gina ]
Can 't believe it .
A tire iron
requires a lot of ...
- Wow .
- I know .
[ instrumental squealing ]
[ swallowing ]
[ sighs ]
- No , you don 't . No , you don 't .
- [ Eden wails ]
No , you don 't .
No . No . No !
- Will .
- [ glass clatters ]
Jesus .
[ laughing ]
Sorry .
You scared me .
No harm done .
You 're so handsome
tonight .
You 're shining .
And , Kira ,
you 're both
really beautiful .
Thank you .
Heh .
Could you help me
get those glasses , please ?
Bars on windows are new .
Well , I was here
alone for a while .
It 's security ,
safer .
It 's nice .
Thank you .
We got them
in Mexico .
Is that where you 've been
for the last two years ?
Some of the time .
Did you
worry about me ?
Did you think
about me ?
Yeah .
I did .
Well , I 'm fantastic .
I 've never
been better .
You don 't have to worry
about me anymore .
You don 't find it hard
to be in this house again ?
No , not at all .
It doesn 't
have to be .
That 's what 's
so incredible .
You look different , Edie .
I am different .
I 'm free .
All that useless pain ,
it 's gone .
It 's something
anyone can have , Will ,
and I want you
to have it , too .
[ Ben ] Eden looks hot .
I can say that ,
right ?
We 're all
consenting adults .
[ groans ]
It 's good to see you
again , Ben .
You , too .
It 's been
way too long .
Heh .
I 'm just here
for the food .
What were you guys
talking about ?
[ guests chattering ]
Not my business .
I was just
telling Will
that pain
is optional .
It is ?
Why didn 't anyone
tell me that before now ?
[ laughs ] I know .
But it 's actually
really simple .
All those
negative emotions ,
grief , anger ,
depression ,
is all just
chemical reactions .
It 's entirely physical ,
and it 's completely
changeable .
Kind of sound like
a pamphlet there , Eden .
You can actually expel
those emotions
from your body
and live the life
you want to live .
So you 're
shitting out your pain ?
I can see you 're
not interested .
I 'm sorry , Eden .
It just sounds
fucking crazy .
Eden , what the fuck ?
Until you
stop making a joke
out of everything ,
you 'll never
learn a thing .
That 's why nobody
cares what you think .
[ chuckles ]
Um ...
yeah . Okay .
Heh .
She fucking
gored me , man .
That was loud .
[ guests chattering ]
- Oh , it 's not - -
- For the vegetarians .
Has she been acting
like this all night ?
Yeah . David , too .
Look , I 'm all for whatever
you gotta do to get by ,
especially you two ,
with what you went through ,
but you didn 't lose
your mind .
Oh , I didn 't ?
Not like that .
How are you ?
I don 't know .
I don 't really know
how to act .
Well , it 's not like
the good old days
anymore , you know .
No .
No , it isn 't .
Wait . Where 's Amanda ?
Home with the kids .
- Yeah ?
- Pissed .
What ? What 's up ?
Think we hate
each other .
That 's not good .
Yeah . I know .
But the sex is - -
it 's so ...
- angry .
- [ laughs ]
[ laughs ]
I can 't get away
from it , man .
Um , it 's good to see you .
You , too .
Mm .
Hey , no one cares
what I think ?
No .
Come on ? Really ?
Ben , have
a glass of wine .
I 've let it go
already , and
so should you .
I 'll always
have a drink .
See ?
It 's gone already .
♪ And listen to the sky ... ♪
We 'll be here .
Come .
Sit with me .
Ask me a question .
Okay .
[ sighs ]
Seriously ,
ask me a question .
Okay . Sorry .
Um - - Hey , wait .
- You 're up for tenure ,
aren 't you ?
- Yeah . I got it .
Come on .
A year ago .
Year ago ? Really ?
I had a party
and everything .
I 'm ... sorry .
You don 't have
to be sorry .
You 're here now .
♪ And will some loving
ease your pain ? ♪
- ♪ And will the silence ... ♪
- [ chattering ]
It 's weird to be here ,
isn 't it ?
Mm .
♪ And will
the swallows come again ? ♪
Maybe that 's Choi ,
our hero .
Fucking Choi .
- Hey .
- [ door opens ]
[ David ] Aha .
Yeah , look .
I 'm finally here .
Yeah .
Who 's that ?
[ guests chattering ]
Hey .
Um , everybody ...
[ squeals ]
It 's you .
Oh , darlin ' .
Oh , I can 't believe
you 're really here .
This is
my friend Pruitt .
- Hey .
Evening .
[ singing in Spanish ]
Eden .
How are you ?
Mm .
Hey . I 'm Ben .
Nice to meet you .
I 'm gonna grab
a whiskey . Did you
want anything ?
Ah , anything diet
is fine , thanks .
Okay .
Hey . I 'm Tommy .
Miguel , Kira , Gina .
Nice to meet you .
I have no idea .
I 'm glad
you 're here ,
but frankly where
the hell is Choi ?
Choi ?
Is my asshole boyfriend .
Said he was gonna be
early for once .
He didn 't call you guys ,
say he was gonna be late ?
No . Come on .
I thought he was
gonna come with you .
- [ Gina ] Yeah , I - -
- We haven 't seen him .
All right , that 's it .
I 'm gonna try again .
Heh . Do you guys
have service up here ?
- [ chuckles ]
- Sorry .
Horrible .
And the bills fell
through the cracks
while we were away .
We have to get
them up here
and reconnect
the landline .
I 'm sorry , Gina .
Well , he usually calls
at least once .
You know what ?
Your best bet
is gonna be
in the back actually .
Good luck , though .
[ lock clicks ]
Is everything okay ,
Will ?
Yeah . Yeah , why didn 't
you leave the key
in the door , though ?
There was a home invasion
up in the canyon
about a month ago .
- Oh .
- This couple got terrorized .
It was really sick .
Just kinda
freaked us out .
I didn 't hear about it .
Then I 'm sure
it never happened .
Yeah , come on ,
Will .
Can 't a man
put himself
in lockdown
if he wants ?
This is America .
Okay , what if
there was a fire ?
Okay .
There you go .
Better ?
I just keep
the house a little
differently .
That 's all .
It 's my house .
Will , could you
do me a favor
and go get
some more
firewood ?
You know
where we keep it .
[ chatter resumes ]
Has he been
like this a lot ,
so agitated ?
[ Kira ] Sometimes .
Well , I 'm glad
he has you .
It comforts me .
I know he wants
the best for you , too .
I 'm glad
you 're here , Kira .
I think
it 's important .
Can I ask you
something ?
How has he been
handling things ?
He can be
self-destructive .
I think he 's doing
the best he can .
[ children speaking
indistinctly ]
- [ laughter ]
- You 're it .
You 're it ! Come on !
[ children chattering ]
[ chatter stops ]
[ muted chattering ]
[ wood clunks ]
Come back to us
when you 're ready .
[ water splashing ]
[ Will ] I 'm telling you .
[ Eden ]
Why are you doing it ?
Because it 's - -
You 're very dirty here .
- Am I ?
- Yes .
[ laughs ]
And it 's
attention to detail
that is
incredibly important .
It 's my credo .
It 's your credo ?
It 's a new - -
I came up with it
last night . Hey .
Why don 't you go
back to bed , okay ?
We 'll keep - -
We 'll keep it down .
- Okay .
- [ Eden laughs ]
Okay . I love you .
Good night , baby .
Good night .
I love you , too . Night .
Good night , hon .
Mm .
And that 'll be
the time he saw
his gross parents
having sex .
[ laughs ] We are gross .
- [ laughs ]
- Mmm .
Do you think
he needs a brother ?
[ woman screams ]
No ! Oh , my - -
They 're in a cult .
No , no , stop .
We 're not in a cult .
I know plenty of people
who do the invitation .
- You do ?
- Yeah , yeah .
Eden , you guys
really in this ?
We are .
So that 's why
you were in Mexico ?
Did you get
all naked down there
in the jungle ?
Sometimes .
Well , I did .
[ laughter ]
Yeah , you did .
But , you know ,
it 's just - -
It 's just
a group of people
coming together .
You know , they all
have lost someone ,
and then they - -
they help each other .
You know ,
it 's really a science
rather than , like ,
some weird religious cult
or anything .
You know ,
it 's smart people
like - - like us ,
here in L.A. ,
New York ,
thousands of people .
You 'd be surprised .
Yeah , my boss
is into it .
It 's like a new EST
or something , right ?
Yeah , no - -
I think
it 's a little more
grounded than that ,
you know ,
more practical .
And at the same time ,
it 's very spiritual ,
you know ,
however you define that .
Seriously ,
what goes on down there ?
I mean , is it
like a self-help group
thing or ...
Well ...
since you asked ,
we have something
that we 'd like
to show you .
- David .
- Oh , no .
- Yes , yes .
- [ chatter ]
- No , no .
- Perfect . Just perfect .
- Oh , no . Now I understand
- why the doors are locked .
- My bad .
You 're gonna
convert us .
This is
a conversion thing ,
right ?
Oh , my God .
No , this is
the real reason ?
I know it sounds
a little weird ,
but it 's actually - -
it 's pretty amazing stuff .
Indulge us , okay .
Is this some kind
of a recruitment video ?
I really
don 't want to - -
I do . Convert me .
I am weak .
Yeah , you are .
It 's nothing like that .
Promise .
All right , let 's do this .
[ music playing ]
[ man ] This is our home
in Sonora , Mexico ,
and it is your home , too ,
if you choose it to be .
- [ snickers ]
- Our home and our family
is open to anyone
with the desire
to help themselves .
The human brain has
a remarkable ability to heal .
My life 's work
has been to discover
new ways to rewire ,
to rewrite
our experiences with trauma .
I mean , trauma has visited ...
all of us .
We invite you
to a conscious existence ,
to a connected existence .
But we take this journey ,
all journeys side by side .
You are not alone .
Wherever you are ,
we - - we transcend , hmm ?
[ man ]
How do you feel , Annie ?
I feel loved .
[ Annie sighs ]
You are loved .
You are deeply loved .
Who are you
going to see , dear ?
[ deep breath ]
My husband ...
James ...
my father .
It 's all right .
[ Annie sighs ]
They will
all be there .
[ gasping ] I - -
Soon , Annie .
Soon .
[ wheezing ]
Over soon .
All of the pain and
all of the grief ,
you renounced it ,
haven 't you ?
You 've made a choice .
You 're ready to go ,
aren 't you , honey ?
[ Annie wheezing ]
Come .
Come . Breathe in .
Breathe in .
Breathe deeply .
You feel
her spirit ?
I can feel it .
[ wheezing ]
[ wheezing stops ]
[ sighs ]
She 's with
all of us now ...
and your father ...
and your wife ...
and your son .
Don 't cry .
There 's no darkness ,
just reunion .
Annie is safe now .
[ insects chirping ]
[ dog barks ]
This is
what it 's about .
We did not just
watch somebody die .
That was real ?
- Yes , it was .
- Yeah .
Why would anyone
want to watch that ?
She just wanted
to show everyone
that there 's nothing
to be afraid of .
That was the point .
She was very sick .
With what ?
She barely looked 30 .
Cancer .
[ Ben ]
Look , I get it .
If you
gotta go at 30 ,
it 's not a bad way ,
surrounded by people
who love you .
On video ?
It 's beautiful .
[ sighs ]
It 's
a little grim .
She looked
at peace to me .
- I 'm not judging her .
- No , I know , babe .
Yeah , no one 's
judging her .
I just don 't understand
why you 'd show
something like that at
a dinner party , David .
- [ David ] You don 't get it ?
- Mm-mmm .
I guess this is
not really being taken
the way we meant it .
I mean , it is
a pretty heavy thing
to drop on us , David .
But it 's not heavy .
For us , it 's not .
- No .
- [ Pruitt ] It 's okay .
Not everybody gets it .
It 's not about the fact
that she died . We all die .
What 's it about ?
It 's about communion .
Right ,
like Eden said ,
she 's just
trying to show you
that there 's nothing
to be afraid of .
Look at me . My pain
had turned me into
some walking cliché .
I was a coked-up ,
out-of-control
record producer ,
for God 's sake .
I was a slave
to my own grief ,
but not anymore .
Dr. Joseph
freed me from that .
I just ...
phew !
He gave me back
my center , you know ?
I don 't have to be
afraid anymore .
Amen , brother .
[ sighs ]
You know , we 've all been
through horrible things ,
but those things
don 't have to define us .
What happened
to Eden and Will - -
No , don 't . Don 't !
David , don 't .
Finding this
saved my life .
I almost died after .
I almost
couldn 't keep on living .
You know that , Will .
But look at me now .
I 'm great . I 'm happy .
I 'm not angry anymore .
And if anyone is
gonna try to take that
away from me ...
My God , look at the way
you 're looking at me .
[ laughs ]
If anyone is gonna try
to say that this isn 't - -
Edie , I - - Edie - -
It 's just you
don 't think I know ?
Hey , hey , hey , hey , hey .
- I know !
- Let 's get a drink .
It 's just
that easy for you ?
Come on .
Come on . Let 's
get a drink .
Yeah , we all are lost .
We can agree
on that , right ?
It 's just ...
It 's too big .
It 's too big
for any of us alone .
You got to ...
[ doorbell rings ]
That better be - -
No , I 've got it .
I 've got it . I got it .
[ door opens ]
David .
[ David ]
Oh , sorry .
Excuse me for a second .
[ chatter outside ]
[ woman ]
Hi there .
- Hey .
Are you okay ?
I-I 'm sorry .
No , not you .
I mean , I knew it was
gonna be heavy , but ...
I was just - - why Choi and I
were supposed to be
here together for you .
We have to make
a better effort .
It 's on us ,
and I was trying
to give you space ,
and I don 't know
if that came across
like I was checked out .
- It 's ...
- [ chatter continues ]
[ David ] I think
you should probably ...
Okay , hello .
I don 't - -
[ scoffs ]
You haven 't heard
a word I said , have you ?
I-I 'm sorry , Gina .
Just a couple people
looking for a party on foot .
Good luck . They 'll die
of dehydration .
Yeah .
[ guests chatter ]
Anyway , um ,
we can talk later .
I just - - I wanted you
to know that ...
I have been
thinking about you .
- Yeah .
- All right ?
- I love you ...
- I love you , too .
and I miss you .
I miss you , too .
I 'm gonna get a refill .
Get a - - Get a drink .
[ man vocalizing ]
[ guests chatter ]
[ Claire ]
I feel like you guys
have to come to my house .
I - - That 's all I do .
Get ice cream and ...
- [ vocalizing continues ]
- [ chatter continues ]
Are you gonna
come and join us
at some point ?
Will ?
Can you tell me
what that is ?
It is a pill , Will .
I found a bunch of it
in Eden 's bedroom
- unlabeled - -
- Wait . What are you - -
Please just look at it .
It 's phenobarbitol ,
I think .
Is that dangerous ?
Anything is dangerous if
you take too much of it .
It 's a barbiturate .
I mean , it 's old-school ,
but it 's ...
not unusual to find it
if you 're rifling
through somebody 's
medicine cabinet .
Hey , hey , break up
your little clique .
Come talk to us .
Come on . Let 's go .
Apparently
V.I.P. room
is in the kitchen .
Guys ,
guys , guys ,
join us , please .
Just opened
another bottle .
Oh , yes .
Probably needs
a little more air .
I mean it , Miguel .
Just keep it
between us .
Okay , Snoopy .
Ah , man .
Can you give this one
to Miguel ?
- Yeah .
- Gracias .
De nada .
Ah , smell that .
Okay .
Salud .
Will thinks
you guys are on pills .
[ swallows ]
- [ chuckles ]
- Figuratively .
You think we 're crazy ?
I never said that .
That 's okay .
I 'm not offended .
A lot of people
think we 're crazy .
But I doubt they 're
as happy as we are .
[ singing in Spanish ]
Where 's the diet
again ?
Why ?
No comprendo inglés .
- Thank you .
- De nada .
Or don 't you guys think
this is a little bit weird ?
Look , Will ,
there is no way
that tonight
wasn 't gonna feel
a little strange ...
or sad .
Look , this is just
a long-overdue reunion
between old friends
with a couple
of totally frickin '
friend weirdoes .
They 're a little Mansony .
- " Mansonian " ?
- And that skinny girl - -
Look , I 'm not kidding .
Come on .
Hey , I got you .
Look at me .
Yeah , they 're
a little weird ,
but this is L.A.
They 're harmless .
Let 's just get
through this night ,
give them a break .
Let 's steal some more
of this wine .
Oh , now that is
something I can
get behind . Come on .
[ David ] Hey , guys , listen !
I realize that some of you
might have found that video
a little disturbing
or off-putting ,
and I apologize for that .
It 's cool .
Nah , Gina , it 's not .
Last thing I want
you guys to think
is that I 'm trying
to force my ideas on you .
- [ Ben ] Welcome back .
- Hey .
You know ,
it 's just I want
you guys to know me .
There 's this game we
used to play in Mexico
at the end of group ,
and I think
we should try it .
What kind of game
are we talking about ?
[ Kira ] Like charades
or something ?
Ah , it 'll be fun ,
and it 'll give you a sense
of what we learned , right ?
I 'm in .
What is it ?
Okay , it 's kind of
like that game
we played in college ,
" I never . "
- Oh , yeah .
- I always lose that game .
Oh , I never do .
Except this time ,
it 's " I want , "
so we take turns ,
and everybody gets
to say what they want .
I want to hear
what Gina did in college .
You mean
who she did .
[ mouths words ]
The point is
to be honest .
All right ? To admit
your desires .
You know ,
because anything
is possible
once you strip away
social constraints
and embarrassment
and those negative emotions
that , you know - -
the things
that hold us down .
So honesty , okay ?
That 's what it 's about .
Want to give it a shot ?
I 'll go first .
Wonderful .
Okay . I want ...
to tell you ,
Eden , and David ...
Will and Kira
and Gina ,
Miguel ...
Pack a lunch .
and Tommy - -
There are so many .
Ben , Claire , Pruitt ...
I want to tell you all
that I love you .
I know I haven 't known
some of you for very long ,
but tonight I feel love .
I do .
And a lot of people
don 't say that .
They 're afraid .
But - - So , I love you .
- Oh .
- Mm .
- Oh , shit .
- Oh , my .
Oh , my gosh .
[ laughs ]
This is ...
Wow .
Hi there .
[ David ]
You got it ?
Uh-huh .
All right .
Um ...
I want ...
some of that coke
you used to do .
Done . I think
I might have some more .
You keep it
in the house ?
You 're
the worst rehabber
in the world .
No , David , don 't .
I was kidding .
No , you weren 't .
That 's okay .
That 's the point
of the game .
Okay .
I wasn 't kidding .
Bust that shit out .
[ laughter ]
There you go .
I like
this game .
I want to tell you
about my wife
Margaret .
We were married
eight years ,
would have been 15
next month .
She was a painter , oils .
First saw her work
at this artists retreat
in Minneapolis .
I was in love with her
before I even met her .
These abstract ,
energetic landscapes ...
And then I saw her .
[ scoffs ]
Wow . It was like
I 'd hit the jackpot .
She was the most generous
spirit I 'd ever seen ,
and she was as bright
and gorgeous as ...
the morning .
When you surprised her ,
she had this - - this laugh ,
this joyous ,
guttural rumble
that came from
way down deep inside .
You knew you 'd done
something good .
She was all light ,
all light .
During times
like this , um ,
nights like
this night ...
I think of her
quite a bit .
Did she , uh ,
pass away ?
Yes , she did .
We had
been drinking .
I had been drinking .
We had
just come home
from a dinner ,
and we were
in the kitchen .
We 'd fell into one
of those arguments ,
you know ,
one of those
stupid fights
that last
your whole marriage .
It was
about the dishes .
Somebody
started yelling .
I don 't
remember who .
I went to pour myself
another drink .
She tried to stop me ,
and ...
something just gave .
I turned and hit her
as hard as I could .
Her knees buckled .
She hit her head .
Think she was trying
to get back up .
You know , she had
her hand out ,
was staring at me .
And then
she collapsed ,
and she was gone .
What the fuck ?
It was a terrible ,
terrible mistake .
It was seven years ago .
I went to prison .
I paid that way ,
but I was still
the same person .
Finally , by accepting
the invitation ...
and looking only ahead ,
destroying that
horrible part of me
that made
that moment possible ...
I 'm cured .
And I miss her .
Not a day goes by
I don 't think of her .
But I don 't grieve ,
and I don 't
feel guilty anymore .
I 've chosen
to let that go .
Those emotions
are useless ,
because I 'm gonna be
seeing her again
in a better place
than this .
That 's what we believe .
That 's what most people
have believed
for centuries .
I , for one ,
can 't wait to get there .
But forgiveness
doesn 't have to wait .
I 'm free
to forgive myself ,
and so are you .
It 's a beautiful thing .
It really is .
What 's more honorable ,
facing the truth or
hiding it to be accepted ?
And people change .
I don 't know .
This ...
doesn 't seem
very honest .
It feels like you 're
selling us something .
No , we aren 't .
I want ...
Are we really
gonna keep
doing this ?
- I want - -
- This better be good .
I want to kiss Ben .
I always have .
[ laughs ]
Why the hell not ?
Bring it , sister .
[ Claire ]
Oh , my God .
I want
to kiss Ben .
One per party .
- Um , no .
- Boom . No ?
- Whoo !
- Oh !
- Oh , yeah !
- Get it , girl !
[ Gina whooping ]
- Ah !
- Get it , girl .
Go !
Jeez .
I don 't know
if I approve that .
And nobody
tells Amanda .
Uh , I want a blow job ...
Oh , you 're
ridiculous .
from somebody .
Oh , I know .
[ laughter ]
What ?
I 'm not joking .
I have to go .
No , come on .
We 're just having fun .
It 's all right .
This is all making me
a little uncomfortable .
I 'm sorry .
Come on . I 'll - -
Have a seat .
I 'll get you a drink .
We 'll do
something else .
No , no , no .
I don 't want
to spoil
anyone 's fun .
This just
isn 't my thing .
- Claire , please .
- Hey , just - -
Just let her go , David .
Why can 't she just leave ?
Will , I just
want her to stay
and have a good time ,
and Eden has
planned this night
for a long time .
We 'll be
very disappointed .
Yeah , well , just let her
do what she wants , okay ?
I 'm gonna leave .
Of course .
- Bye .
I 'm sorry
if I 've made you
feel uncomfortable .
It 's - - It 's okay .
I 'm tired .
Claire ,
why don 't you just stay
a little longer ?
I 'll see you again
soon , okay ?
I 'm really sorry .
Okay , Claire .
[ David ]
Eden , it 's okay .
I know .
Do you want me
to walk you to your car ?
It 's , like ,
40 feet , Will .
Bye .
- Bye , Claire .
- Bye .
- Nice meeting you .
Are you
in the Prius ?
Yeah .
I parked
behind you .
- [ murmuring ]
- Bye . Thank you , guys .
- What ?
- Why did she leave ?
[ guests murmuring ]
[ Kira ] Hey , Will ,
come over here ,
and talk to me .
Just give me a sec .
[ Miguel ]
So what do you do ?
- [ Pruitt ] Okay .
- Well , I 'm a nurse 's assistant .
Careful on the right .
[ Pruitt ]
Okay .
Straight out .
You 're all set .
Oh , uh , Claire .
[ clears throat ]
- Miguel .
- I save lives .
[ Gina ] Stop .
Will , come on .
Can you and I talk
alone for a minute ?
It 's important .
Yeah . Yeah .
Come on .
I 'm very happy
you 're here .
It 's so important
to Eden and me .
I mean , we chose you
because you matter to us .
You chose me ?
To be here tonight .
But I don 't know , man .
Y-You 've been acting so ...
suspicious
of our hospitality .
Frankly ,
it upsets me a little .
I lock the door ,
and you have a fit about it .
Just now , my friend
wants to move his car ,
and you 're standing
by the window
like you 're gonna catch him
stealing something .
You seem very distant ,
very ...
just off somehow .
I 'm sorry .
Maybe I wasn 't prepared
to be here tonight .
Okay .
I appreciate your honesty .
Look , I - - I understand
that you feel
like you have to be
on the lookout .
I know , because
that 's how I felt .
The world is unsafe
and chaotic ,
and , you know ,
it happened before .
It can always
happen again .
David , please .
I don 't pretend to know
what you went through
with your wife ,
and you don 't know me .
You can 't .
[ door opens ]
[ door closes ]
Hey .
Hi .
I tried to convince
Claire to stay .
I felt bad about ,
uh , my story
scaring her .
She seemed
to understand .
[ music playing ]
[ music continues ]
[ muted conversation ]
[ Ben ] No , I swear to God ,
every day .
Every day I get an email ,
and it 's just I 'm going ,
you know , " What is this ?
Is this , like , gonna
kill my hard drive ? "
And it 's usually some stupid
fricking video of , like - -
How many cat videos
has Claire sent you ?
- Oh , my God .
- Claire has sent me cat videos
so - - Every day ,
it 's a cat video .
I mean ,
I got a cat video .
I got a penguin video .
Oh , my God , penguins .
Penguins are overrated .
- Overrated ?
- Yeah . Yeah .
- They are .
- Here we go .
- Penguins ?
- Yeah , they 're happy ,
[ fading ]
and they 're always like ,
" Oh , my God .
They 're so adorable . "
[ conversation fades ]
[ music playing ]
[ children laughing ]
[ Child ] You 're it .
[ child shrieks ]
[ chewing echoes ]
[ swallows ]
[ rips ]
[ splashing ]
[ chews ]
[ laughter ]
[ shriek ]
Kira .
[ music continues ]
[ wailing ]
[ no audible yell ]
[ insects chirping ]
I need help , Tommy .
Oh , what ?
[ overlapping chatter ]
[ soft growling ]
[ growling continues ]
[ woman laughs ]
[ no audible sounds ]
[ chuckles ]
[ soft scream ]
[ insects chirping ]
[ dog barking ]
So things aren 't great
with Kira , huh ?
Heh . What - -
Why would you say that ?
Just seems
like that to me .
Seems like
she 's real distant .
No .
No , she 's great .
[ coyotes howling ]
Should we go
back inside ?
No . I 'm gonna
make a call .
Oh , good luck .
There 's no service
up here .
No , it goes in and out .
I could hang with you .
You could fuck me
right here .
What ?
Why should we
deny ourselves ever ?
It 's what it was like
in Mexico .
Man , everyone was
just going for it .
It was awesome .
I think you need
to go back inside .
You don 't like me ?
I don 't know you .
I could make you
like me so much .
I could
make you beg me .
Could do it
without even
touching you ...
just with
my voice ...
my breath .
S-Sadie .
You can hurt me
if you want .
I don 't want
to hurt you .
I don 't believe you .
Hey . What are you
doing out here ?
[ coyote yips ]
I needed a break .
Oh , really ?
Heh heh . From what ?
Tommy , there 's
something wrong here .
Will - -
Something bad
is happening here .
You 're wrong .
Look , and I know
what you 're gonna say ,
but Claire left
because that poor girl
is sexually awkward .
Choi is the most
unreliable Korean
in Los Angeles .
He could be anywhere .
And Eden ...
I haven 't seen her
for two years .
It 's crazy .
But we 're all
trying to figure out
how to go on ,
you know .
This is how they do it .
Something doesn 't
feel safe here .
Of course
it doesn 't feel safe .
Took a lot of courage
for you to come here tonight ,
but you 're letting your mind
run away with things .
Hey ...
I love you , Will .
But you gotta stop acting
so fucking weird .
It 's freaking people out .
You 're safe , okay ?
I 'll see you back inside .
[ coyotes yipping ]
[ helicopter buzzing ]
[ cell phone beeps ]
Will , Choi .
What 's up ?
Listen ,
it 's about 7 : 00 ,
and I 'm pulling up
to Eden 's house .
I forgot to pick up
dessert like I said
I would ,
and I can 't
get ahold of Gina .
Could you get some
on your way ? I - -
Look ,
I 'm early , dude .
I 'm actually early ,
but honestly
I don 't want to go
back down the hill
and look
for a fucking
patisserie .
I hope
you get this .
See you here
in a few , I guess .
I 'm goin ' in .
Okay , bye .
[ music playing ]
There he is .
- See ?
- Hey , buddy .
All right , I want
to play " I want . "
- I want - -
- No more blow jobs .
I like this game .
Was it obvious that
I like the game ?
I have room .
I could do it .
We both enjoyed
that game .
We did . Heh .
- Oh .
- Ooh .
[ Gina ] I think
this is a new game .
- [ joking ] I 'm scared .
- This is the next game .
[ chuckles ]
Maybe this is one
of those guess who ...
- [ gasping ]
- So pretty .
- So purty .
- Nice .
[ Kira ] It is lovely .
Stop it right now .
What is going on here ?
Happy birthday .
What is this about ?
It 's not for another week .
It 's close enough . Mwah .
- Okay , please , please .
- Come on .
But no singing .
- Oh , come on .
- Come on .
Please ? Please ? Thank you .
- It 's wish time .
- All right .
Make it good .
- [ blows ]
- Yeah .
[ applause ]
You attacked
that one .
- Bastard .
- Well done .
Where 's Choi ?
Excuse me ?
I mean , where the fuck
is Choi , hmm ?
What are you
talking about , Will ?
I just got
a message from him .
He said he was here , that he
had gotten here at 7 : 00 .
- What ?
- He said he was here .
Eden ,
is that true ?
I haven 't
seen Choi tonight .
Edie , where is he ?
Will , stop , please .
Just - -
No . No . I just
got a message from him .
He said he was here .
He made the call
from right outside .
- We haven 't seen him .
- Don 't fucking lie to me .
He called
from right outside
your front door .
David is not
lying to you .
Choi never got here .
Maybe he
turned around , man .
Look , he might
have forgotten
something , Will .
You never know .
Yeah , why is everyone
acting so fucking polite ?
[ scoffs ]
Where 's Choi ?
Hey , Eden ,
what 's going on ?
I have not seen
Choi tonight ,
Gina , I swear .
Something
isn 't right here .
There is something
very strange going on here ,
and no one
is saying anything .
What do you think
is happening , Will ?
Hey , who are you ? Hmm ?
See , see , I don 't get
why you two are here .
Hey , these are
my guests .
Yeah . Hmm .
Two years . We don 't
see you for two years ,
and then all of a sudden ,
we get invited
to this lavish dinner .
You 're all smiles ,
spewing out all this jargon
with these two in tow .
Don 't tell me
that this is normal ,
- the invitation .
- It helps people .
Will , everybody 's
allowed to have - -
No , it 's a fucking cult ,
Miguel !
It 's a fucking cult !
Will , sit down !
No ! No , look at
the video , okay ?
It 's not about communion .
It 's not about family .
It 's about fucking denial .
You are
out of line .
All right , no ,
it 's about denial .
Oh , you know what it is ?
It 's a fucking brainwash .
Our son died , Edie ,
and you 're trying to ignore it .
It meant something
when he died ,
and don 't you try
to erase that .
Ty was real . It was rea - -
It is real .
Please , please , Edie .
Where 's Choi ?
Will , she said
she doesn 't know .
I think
this is just a big
misunderstanding .
Don 't fucking
patronize me , David .
Hey , why don 't you
tell me something ?
Why are all the doors
locked , huh ?
Oh , my God .
Okay , why are all the bars
on the windows , hmm ?
Why is there
a big fucking bottle
of phenobarbitol
stashed in your bedroom ?
Jesus Christ , Will .
Did you go through
our things ?
I 'm sorry . I 'm sorry .
We should go .
- No . No . No .
- We should go .
Something very dangerous
is going on here ,
and nobody 's
talking about it .
We 're all
just ignoring it
because David brought out
some good wine !
We are going , Will .
We are going .
No , I 'm not
going anywhere !
We are going
right now , Will .
[ doorbell rings ]
[ David ]
It 's all right .
All right .
- [ door opens ]
- What 's up ?
Choi ?
I 'm so sorry .
I was right here ,
and then work called ,
and it 's so fucked up ,
' cause they can 't do
anything without me .
[ Choi ] I called you .
I didn 't get it .
[ Choi ]
You okay ?
Hi , love .
Did I miss dinner ?
You missed more
than that , bud .
We have plenty .
I 'll get you something .
I 'll fix him
a plate .
[ Eden ]
Thank you , Pruitt .
[ footsteps echo
on stairs ]
What 's going on ?
David ...
It 's okay .
We really should
go now , Will .
Just give him
a minute , Kira .
I 'm - - I 'm sorry , Eden .
I know it 's hard , Will ,
but you
can 't criticize us
for finding our own way
through this .
I 've never done that
to you .
I know . I know .
It 's none of my business .
I know ,
and I 'm very sorry .
It 's okay .
You 're part
of our family , Will .
All of you are .
[ footsteps echoing
on stairs ]
Will you - - Will you
excuse me for a second ?
Choi , eat .
You - - You got
any more of that wine ?
[ Will ]
Just gotta lather it up .
Keep washing .
10 seconds ,
at least .
[ water rushes ]
[ rushing stops ]
[ insects chirping ]
We should go .
Let 's go , then .
Let 's just - -
Let 's just
get out of here .
I can 't .
Kira , I 'm not okay .
My son is dead .
Where do I put that ?
I don 't know .
It 's like a scream
trapped inside me .
And nothing
changes the fact
that I should have - -
I should have
been watching
more closely that day .
Now , look , you couldn 't
have known , Will .
You could not have been
looking out for that .
It 's another kid .
And Ty loved him .
And they were
just playing .
They were
just messing around .
I shouldn 't have
let them have the bat .
What happened to your son
wasn 't anything
that could be predicted
or changed or ...
I 've been waiting to die
since the moment
it happened .
Moving forward
is not a betrayal , Will .
Look at Eden .
That 's what
letting go looks like .
You 're not
letting go of him .
I would never ask you to .
You know that .
We can help
each other , Will .
That 's the only way .
I love you , Kira ...
but I don 't think
you can help me .
I 'm sorry .
Yeah , you are .
[ insects chirping ]
Mmm . Red velvet .
Miguel , you get
the first piece .
I 'm excited .
Hi , Will .
Can I see his room ?
Of course .
[ birds chirping ]
[ music playing ]
[ insects chirping ]
[ door slides ]
[ snaps match ]
[ music playing ]
[ Dr. Joseph ]
I know you have doubts .
Skepticism
can be contagious .
I wouldn 't
have known either
before I saw the new truth
and shared it with you .
I wouldn 't have believed ,
but it was revealed
so clearly .
Remember the reward .
This beautiful moment
is upon us .
Tonight is the night
our faith is made real .
The hardest thing
is to start .
Just take the step .
Believe ,
and give yourself over .
[ knock on door ]
[ Pruitt ]
Will , let 's go .
Everybody 's waiting .
I love you .
I love you so much ,
my heart is breaking .
I 'm waiting for you .
[ knock on door ]
Okay .
[ music playing ]
Kira .
Look at these people .
They 're so happy
to be here with you .
I think
we should take a moment
to look at each other
and really look .
Please raise your glass .
[ mouths word ]
To a better world .
To peace .
Cheers .
- Cheers .
Don 't drink it !
Don 't fucking touch it !
- No ! No !
- [ shouting ]
- Will !
- No , don 't drink !
- Don 't drink !
- Calm down , Will .
No . No .
We are leaving now !
- Control yourself .
- Will , you do not
want to go this way .
Let 's go , Kira .
We 're leaving
right now !
- Calm down .
- No , we are leaving now !
You ruined it !
You ruined everything !
[ shrieks ]
Oh , my God .
Sadie .
- Sadie .
- Oh , my God , Will .
What did you do ?
Don 't move her .
Sadie .
Somebody call 911 .
- I 'm on it .
- Sadie .
Sadie , can you hear me ?
[ all murmuring ]
Do you have
a first-aid kit ?
Sadie ,
can you hear me ?
It 's okay , Sadie .
- She 's not breathing .
- No , she 's breathing .
- Not Sadie , Gina .
- What ?
Gina ?
All right , get her
to the floor .
Gina .
What 's going on ? Gina !
- Baby ?
- Gina .
- Can you hear me ?
- Baby ?
Starting CPR .
Baby , it 's gonna be okay .
- What 's happening , Miguel ?
- Somebody get 911 ?
I 'm not getting
any reception .
a pulse , Miguel .
Fucking door 's locked .
- Gina , can you hear me ?
- Gina .
- Come on , Gina .
- Okay , baby .
[ mouthing words ]
[ gunshot ]
[ whimpers ]
[ music playing only ]
[ gunshot ]
[ guests gasping ]
Come on .
Go . Go . Go . Go . Go .
- Tommy . Tom - - Tommy .
- [ gunshot ]
Come on ! Let 's go !
- [ yells ]
- Tommy !
[ yells , grunting ]
[ overlapping yells ]
- Come on !
- Kira ! Kira !
- This way .
- What ? !
Ben , this way !
- Oh , my God .
- Go left . Left !
- [ door rattling ]
- Oh . It 's locked .
Will , it 's locked .
Okay , okay .
This way . This way .
[ shrieks ]
[ yells ]
Will ! Will !
[ shrieks ]
[ grunting ]
- [ pounding on door ]
- [ Sadie wailing ]
- [ pounding , wailing stop ]
- [ footsteps recede ]
The door . The door .
Fuck . It 's locked .
We 're gonna have
to break it .
- [ thumping ]
- [ men yelling ]
Shh . Kira .
- [ yelling outside ]
- [ loud clatter ]
[ both grunting ]
[ yells ]
- [ Will ] No .
- [ Ben ] Please , no .
[ muffled sobs ]
Will , why is
this happening ?
Listen to me .
We are gonna get ready .
We 're gonna do
whatever it takes .
Do you hear me ?
- They are just people .
- Right .
- Okay ?
- Okay .
- Come on .
Okay .
[ Eden ] You weren 't
supposed to hurt
anybody like that .
[ David ] I know .
[ indistinct whispering ]
- [ David ] Oh , God .
- [ Eden ] How could you do that ?
- Why would you do that ?
- Don 't do this .
We were supposed
to just go to sleep
and go there together .
It was supposed
to be beautiful .
It 's gonna be quiet
in a minute .
We 'll be there soon .
It wasn 't supposed
to be like this .
- That 's not what he said .
- No , I know . It 's just ...
we just have
to finish now . Hey .
Listen to me .
We take it
one step at a time .
We finish .
- No . I can 't .
- It 'll be quiet ,
and we can rest .
Yes , you can .
Eden ,
you gotta help me .
You have to help me .
You can 't leave me .
No , this is wrong .
Dr. Joseph said it
was gonna be hard ,
but we 'll have
to finish it now .
This is wrong .
We were chosen ,
remember ?
We were chosen .
This is the only way
we can leave
this hurting .
This is right .
This is the only way
we can stop hurting .
We can
leave all this ,
all this pain ,
all this shit
behind .
You can do this .
Hey ...
we can still
get there .
Come on .
[ Eden crying ]
[ whispering ]
There 's a door
- to the garage upstairs .
- Okay .
We 're going there .
Okay .
[ Eden crying ]
[ David ] Shh . Shh .
[ gasping ]
- [ Eden ] Dr. Joseph ...
- [ door slams ]
[ gasping ]
[ gurgling ]
[ voices echo ]
Oh , my God .
Choi .
Oh , God .
No .
What ?
- No .
- What ?
No . No . There was
a door here .
Oh , fuck .
We had a door here
when we lived here .
Fuck . Okay .
Okay , maybe - -
maybe we can signal
someone outside .
Maybe I can signal
[ gasps ] Come on .
Kira .
- [ grunts ]
- Shh .
- [ footsteps echo on stairs ]
Kira .
[ both grunting ]
[ chuckles ]
Don 't be afraid .
There is a plan
for us , man .
Will .
Just let go . Just -
[ gagging ]
- We 'll be there soon .
I promise .
[ groaning ]
[ groaning continues ]
[ yelling ]
[ yelling stops ]
[ sobbing ]
Come on .
Let 's get out of here .
Eden .
[ gasping ]
I 'm sorry , Will .
I 'm sorry .
Eden .
[ gunshot ]
Stop it . Stop it .
Stop it .
Okay .
Will .
We are not
gonna die like this .
Hey , lis - -
I 'm okay .
[ David ] Eden ?
Get the gun .
Eden ?
[ Will ]
She shot herself , David .
That 's good .
She 's with them now .
It 's empty .
We have a gun .
[ David ] That 's okay .
It 's time .
Don 't do this ,
David .
[ both yelling ]
[ knife slices ]
[ gasping ]
[ Eden coughs ]
Will .
I miss him .
I miss him so much .
I wanted to leave .
[ coughs ]
I 'm sorry .
Will you
take me outside ?
[ Will groans ]
[ sobbing ]
I hope ...
I hope we ...
I , uh ...
I gotta go
get Miguel .
Tommy .
[ distant sirens ]
Okay .
[ dogs barking ]
[ Tommy murmurs ]
[ woman screams ]
[ second woman screams ]
[ helicopter thrumming ]
[ helicopter flies overhead ]
Oh , my God .
[ gunshot echoes ]
[ sirens continue blaring ]
Kira .
[ sirens approaching ]
[ fire engine horn blowing ]
[ multiple sirens echoing ]
[ noise ends ]
[ music playing ]
♪ That I might be
a part of this ♪
♪ Ripple on water
from a lonesome drip ♪
♪ A fallen tree
that witnessed me ♪
♪ Him alone , him and me ♪
♪ And that life itself
could not aspire ♪
♪ To have someone
be so admired ♪
♪ I threw creation to my kin ♪
♪ With a silence broken
by a whispered wind ♪
♪ All of this can be broken ♪
♪ Hold your devil by his spoke ,
and spin him to the ground ♪
♪ And root to root
and tip to tip ♪
♪ I look at him ,
my country drip ♪
♪ Lathered up
by all his fears ♪
♪ But someone brought you
close to tears ♪
♪ Many trains and many miles ♪
♪ Brought you to me
on this sunny isle ♪
♪ And what of which
you wish to speak ♪
♪ Have you come here
to rescue me ? ♪
♪ All of this can be broken ♪
♪ Hold your devil by his spoke ,
and spin him to the ground ♪
♪ But the love of your life
lives , but lies no more ♪
♪ And where she lay ,
a flower grows ♪
♪ And the arms that fed
and the babes that wed ♪
♪ The backs that bled
keeping her in tow ♪
♪ But I am your keeper ♪
♪ And I hold your face
away from light ♪
♪ I am yours till they come ♪
♪ Eye to eye ♪
♪ Nose to nose ♪
♪ Ripping off
each other 's clothes ♪
♪ In a most peculiar way ♪
♪ Eye to eye ♪
♪ Nose to nose ♪
♪ Ripping off
each other 's clothes ♪
♪ In a most peculiar way ♪
[ new song playing ]
♪ Kiss me ♪
♪ O my child ♪
♪ Hold me ♪
♪ Chase me ♪
♪ O my child ♪
♪ Look , see ♪
♪ Innocent ♪
♪ O my child ♪
♪ Wait ♪
♪ My child ♪
[ song ends ]